Guide to the Collection of musical autographs,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series V: Scores
  - Bach "Gavotte." Score and parts for strings., [n.d.], (8 pages bd. a.ms. fair copy, 22 parts a.ms. fair copy) (Box 48, Folder 538)
  - Bach Fugue in A minor. Parts for strings., Metzler & Co.: London, [n.d.], (18 pages bd., 22 parts) (Box 48, Folder 539)
  - Bruch, Max Symphony No. 2. Pc arts for orchestra., Simrock: Berlin, [n.d.], (33 parts) (Box 48, Folder 540)
  - Mozart Mass. No. 12. Parts for orchestra and vocals. Simrock: Bonn and Cologne, [n.d.], (24 parts a.ms. bd., 27 parts ) (Box 48, Folder 541)
    [With handwritten changes. Housed in three folders.]
  - Savino, Domenico Processional. Piano scores and parts for orchestra., G. Schirmer Inc.: USA, [n.d.], (4 pages bd., 4 pages bd. 18 parts) (Box 48, Folder 542)
  - Saint Saens Sarabande et Rigaudon, Opus 93. Score and parts., Breitkopf & Hartel: New York, [n.d.], (29 parts, 1 cover) (Box 48, Folder 543)
  - Saint Saens Marche du Synode: Henry VIII. Score and parts for orchestra., Paris, [n.d.], (36 parts) (Box 48, Folder 544)
  - Schubert, Franz (Peter) Schonka. Parts for orchestra., Furstner: Berlin, [n.d.], (31 parts, 1 part a.ms.) (Box 48, Folder 545)
  - Schumann Symphony No. 2. Score., Whistling: Leipzig, 1861, (232 pages bd.) (Box 48, Folder 546)
  - Tschaikovsky Chant sans paroles. Op. 2, No. 3. Parts for orchestra., Leipzig, [n.d.], (18 parts) (Box 48, Folder 547)